<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryProfileProjectApp</string>
    <string name="bangladesh">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="india">India</string>
    <string name="pakisthan">Pakisthan</string>
    <string name="alert_title">This is a title</string>
    <string name="alert_massege">Do you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_profile">

        The Culture of Bangladesh refers to the way of life of the people of Bangladesh.
        It has evolved over the centuries and encompasses the cultural diversity of several social groups
        of Bangladesh. The Bengal Renaissance of the 19th and early 20th centuries, noted Bengali writers,
        saints, authors, scientists, researchers, thinkers, music composers, painters, and film-makers have played
        a significant role in the development of Bengali culture. The Bengal Renaissance contained the seeds of a
        nascent political Indian nationalism and was the precursor in many ways to modern Indian artistic and cultural
        expression. The culture of Bangladesh is composite and over the centuries has assimilated influences of Islam,
        Hinduism, Buddhism, and Christianity. It is manifested in various forms, including music, dance, and drama; art
        and craft; folklore and folktale; languages and literature; philosophy and religion; festivals and celebrations;


        as well as in a distinct cuisine and culinary tradition.People in Bangladesh are the best of all


    </string>
    <string name="india_profile">
        India (IAST: Bhārat), also called the Republic of India (IAST: Bhārat Gaṇarājya),[19][e] is a country in South Asia.
        It is the seventh-largest country by area, the second-most populous country (with over 1.2 billion people),
        and the most populous democracy in the world. It is bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest,
        and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast. It shares land borders with Pakistan to the west;[f] China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the
        northeast; and Bangladesh and Myanmar to the east. In the Indian Ocean, India is in the vicinity of Sri Lanka and the Maldives.
        India\'s Andaman and Nicobar Islands share a maritime border with Thailand and Indonesia. \n\n

        The Indian subcontinent was home to the urban Indus Valley Civilisation of the 3rd millennium BCE. In the following millennium,
        the oldest scriptures associated with Hinduism began to be composed. Social stratification, based on caste, emerged
        in the first millennium BCE, and Buddhism and Jainism arose. Early political consolidations took place under the Maurya
        and Gupta empires; the later peninsular Middle Kingdoms influenced cultures as far as southeast Asia. In the medieval era,
        Judaism, Zoroastrianism, Christianity, and Islam arrived, and Sikhism emerged, all adding to the region's diverse culture.
        Much of the north fell to the Delhi sultanate; the south was united under the Vijayanagara Empire. The economy expanded
        in the 17th century in the Mughal Empire. In the mid-18th century, the subcontinent came under British East India Company
        rule, and in the mid-19th under British crown rule. A nationalist movement emerged in the late 19th century, which later,
        under Mahatma Gandhi, was noted for nonviolent resistance and led to India's independence in 1947.


    </string>
    <string name="pakisthan_profile">
        The territory that now constitutes Pakistan was the site of several ancient cultures,
        including the Mehrgarh of the Neolithic and the Bronze Age Indus Valley Civilisation,
        and was later home to kingdoms ruled by people of different faiths and cultures, including
        Hindus, Indo-Greeks, Muslims, Turco-Mongols, Afghans, and Sikhs. The area has been ruled by numerous
        empires and dynasties, including the Persian Achaemenid Empire, Alexander III of Macedon, the Indian Mauryan
        Empire, the Arab Umayyad Caliphate, the Gupta Empire,[26] the Delhi Sultanate, the Mongol Empire, the Mughal Empire,
        the Afghan Durrani Empire, the Sikh Empire (partially), and, most recently, the British Empire. \n\n

        Pakistan is the only country to have been created in the name of Islam.[27][28] As a result of the Pakistan
        Movement led by Muhammad Ali Jinnah and the Indian subcontinent's struggle for independence, Pakistan was created in 1947
        as an independent homeland for Indian Muslims.[29] It is an ethnically and linguistically diverse country, with a
        similarly diverse geography and wildlife. Initially a dominion, Pakistan adopted a constitution in 1956, becoming an
        Islamic republic. An ethnic civil war in 1971 resulted in the secession of East Pakistan as the new country of Bangladesh.
        [30] In 1973 Pakistan adopted a new constitution establishing, alongside its pre-existing parliamentary republic status,
        a federal government based in Islamabad consisting of four provinces and three federal territories. The new constitution
        also stipulated that all laws are to conform to the injunctions of Islam as laid down in the Quran and Sunnah.[31]



    </string>
</resources>
